Finding Aid for Harlan Henthorne Hatcher Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- University of Michigan Presidency
  - Yearly Correspondence File
    - 1957-1958
      - News Service (Box 20)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 20)
        (20-21)
      - North Central Association (Box 20)
      - O (Box 20)
        (20-22)
      - Odegaard (C.E.) (Box 20)
      - Olson (Willard C.) (Box 20)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 20)
        (20-23)
      - Phoenix Project (Box 20)
        (20-24)
      - Pierpont (W.K.) (Box 20)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 20)
      - Q-Rz (Box 20)
        (20-25)
      - Radio and Television (Box 20)
        (20-26)
      - Reddig (Rhoda) (Box 20)
      - Regents (Box 20)
      - Relics (Box 20)
        (20-27)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 20)
      - Rowe (Tom) (Box 20)
      - Sa-Sj (Box 21)
        (21-1)
      - Sk-Sz (Box 21)
        (21-2)
      - Sawyer (Ralph) (Box 21)
        (21-3)
      - Science Advisory Committee (Box 21)
      - School Services. Bureau of School Services (Box 21)
        (21-4)
      - South Eastern Michigan Research Corporation (Box 21)
      - Stason (E. Blythe) (Box 21)
        (21-5)
      - Statistical Service (Box 21)
        (21-6)
      - Stevenson (R.A.) (Box 21)
        (21-7)
      - Stirton (W.E.) (Box 21)
      - Student Organizations (Box 21)
        (21-8)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 21)
        (21-9)
      - U (Box 21)
        (21-10)
      - United States Departments and Legislature (Box 21)
      - University Library (Box 21)
        (21-11)
      - University Musical Society (Box 21)
      - Va-Vz (Box 21)
        (21-12)
      - Vroman (Box 21)
      - Visitors (Box 21)
        (21-13)
      - Wa-Wg (Box 21)
        (21-14)
      - Wh-Wz (Box 21)
        (21-15)
      - Watkins (Herbert) (Box 21)
        (21-16)
      - Williams (G. Mennen) (Box 21)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 21)
        (21-17)
    - 1958-1959
      - Aa-Az (Box 21)
        (21-18)
      - Accrediting (Box 21)
        (21-19)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 21)
      - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 21)
      - Alumni Association (Box 21)
        (21-20)
      - American (Box 21)
        (21-21)
      - American Council on Education (Box 21)
        (21-22)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 21)
        (21-23)
      - Ann Arbor Community Chest (Box 21)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 21)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 21)
        (21-24)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 21)
      - Association of American Graduate Schools (Box 21)
      - Associations (Box 21)
        (21-25)
      - Attwood (Box 21)
      - Ba-Bk (Box 22)
        (22-1)
      - Bl-Bz (Box 22)
        (22-2)
      - Barthell (Box 22)
        (22-3)
      - Bartlett (H.) (Box 22)
      - Bonisteel (Roscoe) (Box 22)
        (22-4)
      - Brablec (Carl) (Box 22)
      - Ca-Cn (Box 22)
        (22-5)
      - Co-Cz (Box 22)
        (22-6)
      - Clapp (Box 22)
        (22-7)
      - Clements Library (Box 22)
      - Council of Ten (Box 22)
      - Cross (Box 22)
      - Da-Dz (Box 22)
        (22-8)
      - "Dago Dazzlers" (Box 22)
        (22-9)
      - Doan (Leland) (Box 22)
      - Dorr (Harold) (Box 22)
      - Drama (Box 22)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 22)
        (22-10)
      - Eckert (Otto) (Box 22)
      - Economics Club of Detroit (Box 22)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 22)
        (22-11)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships,etc. (Box 22)
        (22-12)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships,etc. (A-M) (Box 22)
        (22-13)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships,etc. (N-Z) (Box 22)
        (22-14)
      - Football (Box 22)
        (22-15)
      - Ford Company (Box 22)
      - Ford Fund (Box 22)
      - Foreign Students (Box 22)
        (22-16)
      - Fund for Education (Box 22)
      - Furstenberg (Albert) (Box 22)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 22)
        (22-17)
      - Governing Boards. Association of Governing Boards (Box 22)
        (22-18)
      - Ha-Hd (Box 22)
        (22-19)
      - He-Hz (Box 22)
        (22-20)
      - Hannah (John) (Box 22)
        (22-21)
      - Henderson (Algo) (Box 22)
      - Heyns (Roger) (Box 22)
      - Hunting (Box 22)
      - Ia-Iz (Box 22)
        (22-22)
      - Inglis House (Box 22)
        (22-23)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 22)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics. Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 22)
      - International Center (Box 22)
        (22-24)
      - Invitations to Associations, Ann Arbor (Box 22)
      - Ja-Jz (Box 22)
        (22-25)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 22)
        (22-26)
      - La-Lz (Box 23)
        (23-1)
      - Lane Hall (Box 23)
        (23-2)
      - Lewis (J.A.) (Box 23)
      - Ludlow (Box 23)
      - Legislature (Box 23)
        (23-3)
      - Ma-Mc (Box 23)
        (23-4)
      - Md-Mz (Box 23)
        (23-5)
      - Mexico (Box 23)
        (23-6)
      - Mexican Seminar at Medical School (Box 23)
      - Michigan (Box 23)
        (23-7)
      - Michigan College Presidents (Box 23)
      - Michigan Week (Box 23)
        (23-8)
      - Na-Nz (Box 23)
        (23-9)
      - National (Box 23)
        (23-10)
      - Nelson (Box 23)
      - News Service (Box 23)
        (23-11)
      - North Central Association (Box 23)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 23)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 23)
        (23-12)
      - Olson (Willard C.) (Box 23)
      - Outstanding Achievement Awards (Box 23)
        (23-13)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 23)
        (23-14)
      - Pierpont (W.K.) (Box 23)
        (23-15)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 23)
      - Q (Box 23)
        (23-16)
      - Ra-Rz (Box 23)
      - Radio and Television (Box 23)
        (23-17)
      - Reddig (Rhoda) (Box 23)
      - Regents (Box 23)
      - Relics (Box 23)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 23)
      - Rowe (Tom) (Box 23)
      - Russel Award (Box 23)
        (23-18)
      - Russell (John D.) Study (Box 23)
        (23-19)
      - Sa-Sh (Box 23)
        (23-20)
      - Si-Sz (Box 23)
        (23-21)
      - Sawyer (Ralph) (Box 24)
        (24-1)
      - Science Advisory Board (Box 24)
      - Science. Institute of Science (Box 24)
      - Scott (Box 24)
        (24-2)
      - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 24)
      - School Services. Bureau of School Services (Box 24)
        (24-3)
      - Short (R. Perry) (Box 24)
      - Stason (E. Blythe) (Box 24)
      - State Journal (Box 24)
        (24-4)
      - Statistical Service (Box 24)
      - Stirton (W.E.) (Box 24)
        (24-5)
      - Student Organizations (Box 24)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 24)
        (24-6)
      - Thurber (Donald M.D.) (Box 24)
      - U (Box 24)
        (24-7)
      - University (Box 24)
      - United States Departments (Box 24)
        (24-8)
      - V (Box 24)
        (24-9)
      - Vaughan (Henry F.) (Box 24)
      - Vroman (Box 24)
      - Visitors (Box 24)
        (24-10)
      - Wa-Wg (Box 24)
        (24-11)
      - Wh-Wz (Box 24)
        (24-12)
      - Walter (Erich) (Box 24)
        (24-13)
      - Wayne State University (Box 24)
      - Williams (G. Mennen) (Box 24)
        (24-14)
      - Williams (R.L.) (Box 24)
        (24-15)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 24)
        (24-16)
    - 1959-1960
      - Aa-Az (Box 24)
        (24-17)
      - Accrediting (Box 24)
        (24-18)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 24)
      - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 24)
      - Alumni Association (Box 24)
        (24-19)
      - American (Box 24)
        (24-20)
      - American Council on Education (Box 24)
        (24-21)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 24)
        (24-22)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 24)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 24)
        (24-23)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 24)
        (24-24)
      - Association of American Graduate Schools (Box 24)
      - Associations (Box 24)
        (24-25)
      - Attwood (Box 24)
      - Ba-Bn (Box 25)
        (25-1)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 25)
        (25-2)
      - Bartlett (Lynn) (Box 25)
        (25-3)
      - Blair (Box 25)
      - Ca-Cn (Box 25)
        (25-4)
      - Co-Cz (Box 25)
        (25-5)
      - Clements Library (Box 25)
        (25-6)
      - Clippings (Box 25)
      - Council of Ten (Box 25)
        (25-7)
      - Cross (Box 25)
      - Da-Dz (Box 25)
        (25-8)
      - "Dago Dazzlers" (Box 25)
        (25-9)
      - Deans (Box 25)
      - Dorr (Harold) (Box 25)
      - Ea-Em (Box 25)
        (25-10)
      - En-Ez (Box 25)
        (25-11)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 25)
        (25-12)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 25)
        (25-13)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (Box 25)
        (25-14)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (A-M) (Box 25)
        (25-15)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (N-Z) (Box 25)
        (25-16)
      - Football (Box 25)
        (25-17)
      - Ford Company (Box 25)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 25)
      - Foreign Students (Box 25)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 25)
        (25-18)
      - Governing Boards. Association of Governing Boards (Box 25)
        (25-19)
      - Ha-Hh (Box 25)
        (25-20)
      - Hi-Hz (Box 25)
        (25-21)
      - Hannah (John) (Box 25)
      - Henderson (Algo) (Box 25)
        (25-22)
      - Heyns (Roger) (Box 25)
        (25-23)
      - Hubbard (Box 25)
      - Ia-Iz (Box 26)
        (26-1)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 26)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 26)
        (26-2)
      - International Center (Box 26)
      - Invitations to Associations (Ann Arbor) (Box 26)
      - Ja-Jz (Box 26)
        (26-3)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 26)
        (26-4)
      - La-Lz (Box 26)
        (26-5)
      - Lane Hall (Box 26)
        (26-6)
      - Legislature (Box 26)
      - Ma-Mc (Box 26)
        (26-7)
      - Md-Mz (Box 26)
        (26-8)
      - Manley (Box 26)
        (26-9)
      - Matthaei (Frederick) (Box 26)
      - McInally (William K.) (Box 26)
      - Michigan (Box 26)
        (26-10)
      - Michigan College Presidents (Box 26)
      - Michigan Week,1960 (Box 26)
        (26-11)
      - Moore (Earl V.) (Box 26)
        (26-12)
      - Murphy (Irene) (Box 26)
      - Na-Nz (Box 26)
        (26-13)
      - National (Box 26)
        (26-14)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 26)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 26)
      - Nelson (Box 26)
        (26-15)
      - Niehuss (Marvin) (Box 26)
      - North Central Association (Box 26)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 26)
        (26-16)
      - Outstanding Achievement Awards (Box 26)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 26)
        (26-17)
      - Panama Canal (Box 26)
        (26-18)
      - Pierpont (W.K.) (Box 26)
        (26-19)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 26)
        (26-20)
      - Q-Rn (Box 26)
        (26-21)
      - Radio and Television (Box 26)
        (26-22)
      - Reddig (Rhoda) (Box 26)
      - Regents (Box 26)
      - Relics (Box 26)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 26)
      - Rowe (Tom) (Box 26)
      - Ro-Rz (Box 26)
        (26-23)
      - Russel Award (Box 26)
        (26-24)
      - Sa-Sl (Box 27)
        (27-1)
      - Sm-Sz (Box 27)
        (27-2)
      - Sawyer (Ralph) (Box 27)
      - Science and Technology. Institute of Science and Technology (Box 27)
        (27-3)
      - Senate Advisory (Box 27)
      - Stason (E. Blythe) (Box 27)
        (27-4)
      - Stevens (Kenneth) (Box 27)
      - Stevenson (R.A.) (Box 27)
      - Stirton (W.E.) (Box 27)
        (27-5)
      - Student Organizations (Box 27)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 27)
        (27-6)
      - U (Box 27)
        (27-7)
      - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 27)
      - United States Departments (Box 27)
      - University Library (Box 27)
        (27-8)
      - University Press (Box 27)
      - Va-Vz (Box 27)
        (27-9)
      - Vroman (Box 27)
      - Visitors (Box 27)
        (27-10)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 27)
        (27-11)
      - Wayne State University (Box 27)
        (27-12)
      - Wenley (Box 27)
      - Williams (G. Mennen) (Box 27)
      - Williams (R.L.) (Box 27)
        (27-13)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 27)
        (27-14)
    - 1960-1961
      - Aa-Az (Box 27)
        (27-15)
      - Accrediting (Box 27)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 27)
        (27-16)
      - A.R.P.A. (Box 27)
      - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 27)
      - American (Box 27)
        (27-17)
      - American Council on Education (Box 27)
        (27-18)
      - American Council on Education (Box 27)
        (27-19)
      - Ann Arbor Community Chest (Box 27)
        (27-20)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 27)
      - Association of Midwestern Universities (Box 27)
        (27-21)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 27)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 27)
        (27-22)
      - Association of American Graduate Schools (Box 27)
      - Association of American Graduate Schools (Box 27)
        (27-23)
      - Ba-Bn (Box 28)
        (28-1)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 28)
        (28-2)
      - Bacon (Deborah) (Box 28)
        (28-3)
      - Bartlett (H.) (Box 28)
      - Bond (Box 28)
      - Burlingame (Box 28)
        (28-4)
      - Ca-Cn (Box 28)
        (28-5)
      - Co-Cz (Box 28)
        (28-6)
      - Carnegie Corporation (Box 28)
        (28-7)
      - Clark (Box 28)
      - Clements Library (Box 28)
      - Conference Center (Box 28)
      - Council of Ten (Box 28)
        (28-8)
      - Cross (Box 28)
      - Da-Dz (Box 28)
        (28-9)
      - "Dago Dazzlers" (Box 28)
        (28-10)
      - Dorr (Harold) (Box 28)
      - Dramatic Arts Center (Box 28)
        (28-11)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 28)
        (28-12)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 28)
        (28-13)
      - Edison Foundation (Box 28)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 28)
        (28-14)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (Box 28)
        (28-15)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (Box 28)
        (28-16)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (A-G) (Box 28)
        (28-17)
      - Fellowships, Scholarships, etc. (H-Z) (Box 28)
        (28-18)
      - Fontanna (S.G.) (Box 28)
        (28-19)
      - Football (Box 28)
      - Foreign Students (Box 28)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 28)
        (28-20)
      - Ford Motor Company (Box 28)
      - Ga-Gh (Box 28)
        (28-21)
      - Gi-Gz (Box 28)
        (28-22)
      - Governing Boards. Association of Governing Boards (Box 28)
        (28-23)
      - Ha-Hh (Box 28)
        (28-24)
      - Hi-Hz (Box 28)
        (28-25)
      - Hannah (John) (Box 28)
        (28-26)
      - Henderson (Algo) (Box 28)
      - Heyns (Roger) (Box 28)
      - Hubbard (Box 28)
      - Ia-Iz (Box 29)
        (29-1)
      - Institute of Legal Education (Box 29)
        (29-2)
      - Institute of Labor Relations (Box 29)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 29)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 29)
        (29-3)
      - International Association of Universities (Box 29)
        (29-4)
      - International Center (Box 29)
      - Ja-Jz (Box 29)
        (29-5)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 29)
        (29-6)
      - Kellogg Foundation (Box 29)
        (29-7)
      - Kresge Foundation (Box 29)
      - La-Lz (Box 29)
        (29-8)
      - Lane Hall (Box 29)
        (29-9)
      - Lawton (J. Fred) (Box 29)
      - Lecture Series (Box 29)
      - Lewis (Box 29)
      - Legislature (Box 29)
        (29-10)
      - Legislature (Box 29)
        (29-11)
      - Ma-Md (Box 29)
        (29-12)
      - Me-Mz (Box 29)
        (29-13)
      - McInally (William K.) (Box 29)
        (29-14)
      - Michigan (Box 29)
      - Michigan College Presidents (Box 29)
        (29-15)
      - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 29)
      - Michigan Week,1961 (Box 29)
        (29-16)
      - Michigan,1961 (Box 29)
        (29-17)
      - Michigan,1961 (Box 29)
        (29-18)
      - Na-Nz (Box 29)
        (29-19)
      - National (Box 29)
        (29-20)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 29)
      - Nelson (Box 29)
        (29-21)
      - Niehuss (Marvin) (Box 29)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 29)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 29)
        (29-22)
      - Outstanding Achievement Awards (Box 29)
        (29-23)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 29)
        (29-24)
      - Pierpont (W.K.) (Box 29)
        (29-25)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 29)
      - Q (Box 30)
        (30-1)
      - Ra-Rz (Box 30)
      - Radio and Television (Box 30)
        (30-2)
      - Reddig (Rhoda) (Box 30)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 30)
      - Rowe (Tom) (Box 30)
      - Russel Award (Box 30)
        (30-3)
      - Sa-Sh (Box 30)
        (30-4)
      - Si-Sz (Box 30)
        (30-5)
      - Senate Advisory (Box 30)
        (30-6)
      - Stirton (W.E.) (Box 30)
        (30-7)
      - Student Organization (Box 30)
      - Swainson (John) (Box 30)
      - T-U (Box 30)
        (30-8)
      - University Press (Box 30)
        (30-9)
      - United States Departments (Box 30)
      - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 30)
        (30-10)
      - V (Box 30)
        (30-11)
      - Visitors (Box 30)
      - Visitors (Box 30)
        (Italy's Ambassador)
        (30-12)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 30)
        (30-13)
      - Wallace (Box 30)
        (30-14)
      - Wayne State University (Box 30)
      - Williams (Box 30)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 30)
        (30-15)
    - 1961-1962
      - Aa-Az (Box 30)
        (30-16)
      - Accrediting (Box 30)
        (30-17)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 30)
      - A.F.R.O.T.C. (Box 30)
      - Airborne Television Program (Box 30)
        (30-18)
      - Alumni Association (Box 30)
        (30-19)
      - American (Box 30)
        (30-20)
      - American Council on Education (Box 30)
        (30-21)
      - Ann Arbor Community Chest (Box 30)
        (30-22)
      - Applications (Box 30)
      - Association of Midwestern Universities (Box 30)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 30)
        (30-23)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 31)
        (31-1)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 31)
        (31-2)
      - Attwood (Box 31)
      - Ba-Bn (Box 31)
        (31-3)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 31)
        (31-4)
      - Bacon (Deborah) (Box 31)
        (31-5)
      - Bartlett (H.) (Box 31)
      - Botanical Gardens (Box 31)
      - Ca-Cn (Box 31)
        (31-6)
      - Co-Cz (Box 31)
        (31-7)
      - Carnegie Corporation (Box 31)
        (31-8)
      - Chambers (Box 31)
      - Clements Library (Box 31)
      - Council of Ten (Box 31)
        (31-9)
      - Cross (Box 31)
      - Da-Dz (Box 31)
        (31-10)
      - Dearborn Center (Box 31)
        (31-11)
      - Disclaimer Affidavit (Box 31)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 31)
        (31-12)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 31)
        (31-13)
      - Engineering Lab (Box 31)
        (31-14)
      - Fa-Fh (Box 31)
        (31-15)
      - Fi-Fz (Box 31)
        (31-16)
      - Fellowships, etc. (A-L) (Box 31)
        (31-17)
      - Fellowships, etc. (M-Z) (Box 31)
        (31-18)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 31)
        (31-19)
      - Fontanna (Box 31)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 31)
        (31-20)
      - Goebel (Paul) (Box 31)
        (31-21)
      - Governing Boards (Box 31)
      - Grand Valley College (Box 31)
        (31-22)
      - Ha-Hz (Box 32)
        (32-1)
      - Hannah (John) (Box 32)
        (32-2)
      - Hatcher Anniversary (Box 32)
      - Heyns (Roger) (Box 32)
      - Hubbard (Box 32)
      - I (Box 32)
        (32-3)
      - Institute of International Education (Box 32)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 32)
      - International Center (Box 32)
        (32-4)
      - Invitation (Ann Arbor Meetings) (Box 32)
      - Introduction Letters (Box 32)
      - J-K (Box 32)
        (32-5)
      - La-Lz (Box 32)
        (32-6)
      - Law School (Box 32)
        (32-7)
      - Lecture Committee (Box 32)
      - Likert (Rensis) (Box 32)
      - Ma-Mc (Box 32)
        (32-8)
      - Md-Mz (Box 32)
        (32-9)
      - MacCarthy (Alan) (Box 32)
      - Matthaei (Frederick) (Box 32)
      - McInally (William K.) (Box 32)
      - Michigan (Box 32)
        (32-10)
      - Michigan College Presidents (Box 32)
      - Michigan Daily (Box 32)
      - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 32)
        (32-11)
      - Michigan Industrial Ambassadors (Box 32)
      - Michigan League (Box 32)
      - Murphy (Irene) (Box 32)
      - Michigan Week (Box 32)
        (32-12)
      - Na-Nz (Box 32)
        (32-13)
      - National (Box 32)
        (32-14)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 32)
      - Nelson (Box 32)
      - Niehuss (Marvin) (Box 32)
      - North Central Association (Box 32)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 32)
      - O (Box 32)
        (32-15)
      - Outstanding Achievement Awards (Box 32)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 32)
        (32-16)
      - Peace Corps (Box 32)
        (32-17)
      - Pierpont (W.K.) (Box 32)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 32)
        (32-18)
      - Professional Theatre Program (Box 32)
      - Programmed Learning (Box 32)
      - Q-R (Box 32)
        (32-19)
      - Quarterly Review (Box 32)
        (32-20)
      - Radock (Michael) (Box 32)
      - Regents (Box 32)
      - Research Park (Box 32)
        (32-21)
      - Residence Halls (Box 32)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 32)
      - Russel Award (Box 32)
        (32-22)
      - Russian Visitors (Box 32)
        (32-23)
      - Ruthven (Alexander G.) (Box 32)
      - Sa-Sl (Box 32)
        (32-24)
      - Sm-Sz (Box 32)
        (32-25)
      - Senate Advisory (Box 32)
        (32-26)
      - Schoenfield (Box 33)
        (33-1)
      - Smith (Allan) (Box 33)
      - Sorenson (Box 33)
      - Sororities and Fraternities (Box 33)
        (33-2)
      - Stirton (W.E.) (Box 33)
        (33-3)
      - Student Affairs (Box 33)
      - Student Organizations (Box 33)
        (33-4)
      - Swainson (John) (Box 33)
      - Summer (Box 33)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 33)
        (33-5)
      - U (Box 33)
        (33-6)
      - United States Congress (Box 33)
      - United States Departments (Box 33)
        (33-7)
      - U.S. Dept. of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 33)
      - University (Box 33)
        (33-8)
      - Va-Vz (Box 33)
        (33-9)
      - Venezuelan Students (Box 33)
      - Vroman (Box 33)
      - Visitors (Box 33)
        (33-10)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 33)
        (33-11)
      - Wayne State University (Box 33)
        (33-12)
      - Whiting (Allen) (Box 33)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 33)
        (33-13)
    - 1962-1963
      - Aa-Az (Box 33)
        (33-14)
      - Accrediting (Box 33)
        (33-15)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 33)
      - Airborne Television (Box 33)
      - American (Box 33)
        (33-16)
      - American Council on Education (Box 33)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 33)
        (33-17)
      - Arms Control Symposium (Box 33)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 33)
        (33-18)
      - Ba-Bn (Box 33)
        (33-19)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 33)
        (33-20)
      - Ca-Cn (Box 33)
        (33-21)
      - Co-Cz (Box 33)
        (33-22)
      - Carnegie Corporation (Box 33)
        (33-23)
      - Council of Ten (Box 33)
      - Da-Dz (Box 33)
        (33-24)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 33)
        (33-25)
      - Edison Foundation (Box 33)
      - Emancipation Proclamation (Box 33)
        (33-26)
      - Extension Service (Box 33)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 34)
        (34-1)
      - Fellowships, etc. (Box 34)
        (34-2)
      - Fellowships, etc. (A-I) (Box 34)
        (34-3)
      - Fellowships, etc. (J-Z) (Box 34)
        (34-4)
      - Forsyth (Box 34)
        (34-5)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 34)
        (34-6)
      - Governing Boards (Box 34)
        (34-7)
      - Ha-Hg (Box 34)
        (34-8)
      - Hh-Hz (Box 34)
        (34-9)
      - Henick (Box 34)
        (34-10)
      - Housing (Box 34)
        (34-11)
      - Ia-Iz (Box 34)
        (34-12)
      - Indirect Costs for Research (Box 34)
        (34-13)
      - Institute for Defense Analysis (Box 34)
        (34-14)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 34)
        (34-15)
      - Invitations (Ann Arbor) (Box 34)
        (34-16)
      - Introduction Letters (Box 34)
      - J-K (Box 34)
        (34-17)
      - Kresge Hearing Research Institute (Box 34)
        (34-18)
      - La-Lz (Box 34)
        (34-19)
      - Ma-Mz (Box 34)